好吧，那么……
Okay, so...
看这里，唐格伍德附近的老克隆尼亚大酒店
now here's an old Colonial
inn near Tanglewood.
－唐格伍德是什么东西？
－那里可以欣赏到古典音乐
￡- What's Tanglewood?
￡- They have classical music.
这是音乐会的时间表
Here's the concert
schedule.
这是我脸上的表情
And here's my face.
或者我们也可以住在广场酒店
Or we can stay
at The Plaza,
在太阳饭店吃饭，再看场演出
eat at Le Cirque
and see a show.
不去，我爸妈总是取笑那些住广场酒店的人
No, my parents make fun of people
who stay at The Plaza.
－我的父母就住广场酒店
－唔……
￡- My parents stay at The Plaza.
￡- Eh...
好吧
Okay, all right.
那么，你父母觉得艾德朗戴克山怎么样？
Then how do your parents feel
about the Adirondacks?
去那儿有什么可干的？
What do you do there?
租一间很不错的别墅
看看这个
You rent a nice house.
Look at this.
紧邻湖畔
Right on the lake.
我们要呆在别人的房子里？
We'd be staying
in someone else's house?
他们不会在那儿的
They won't be there.
我不想睡在别人睡过的床上
l don't sleep where
other people have slept.
那你以为旅馆是什么？
What do you think
hotels are?
你在嚷嚷？
你干嘛要嚷嚷？
You're yelling.
Why are you yelling?
因为你什么地方都不想去
Because you don't wanna
go anywhere.
我想去的，相信我
l do, believe me.
只不过你刚才说的那些
都不是很有趣
lt's just that nothing
you've mentioned sounds fun yet.
好吧，那你来选
Okay, then you pick.
只要你觉得好，我们就去
And whatever sounds
fun to you we'll do.
－你想让我来选？
－是的，雷！
￡- You want me to pick?
￡- Yes, Ray!
因为我们去哪儿并不重要
只要我们能够在一起
Because it doesn't matter where we go
as long as we can be together!
－好了，冷静点
－好吧
￡- All right, let's calm it down.
￡- All right.
我只不过太想去了
lt's just that l really
want to do this.
－我也是
－好吧
￡- Me too.
￡- Okay!
参观本和杰瑞的冰激凌工厂
A tour of Ben & Jerry's
ice cream factory.
这也能算是旅行？
Can that be a trip?
是的，能算
Yes, it can.
因为这家工厂在佛蒙特
Because the factory's
in vermont.
看，野花盛开遍野
See, the wild flowers
are blooming.
我们还可以住在这座可爱的家庭旅馆里
And we can stay
at this cute bed and breakfast.
我们为什么不干脆住在
本和杰瑞的房子里？
Why don't we just stay
at Ben & Jerry's house?
我马上打电话去佛蒙特
l'm calling vermont.
免费样品
Free samples.
我打赌肯定是个陷阱
l'll bet
there's a catch.
嘿，很好看
Hey, that's cute.
天啊
God.
艾米，我明天就要去佛蒙特了
Amy, l'm going to vermont
tomorrow.
却没有什么好衣服可以穿
l have nothing to take
on this trip.
但你有一个老公
You have a husband.
那代表了很多东西
Lots of things
go with that.
现在我愿意用他来换一条
Right now l'd trade him
for a pair of pants
让我的屁股看起来小一点的裤子
that make my butt
look smaller.
你知道什么才能使你的屁股看起来小一点吗？
You know what makes
your butt look smaller?
一个老公
A husband.
那么，罗伯特还没有和别人约会？
So, Robert hasn't started
dating anyone else yet?
你是指从我们刚才在女鞋柜台谈论他以后？
You mean since we talked
about him in the shoe department?
我知道，我知道
l know, l know.
试试这件
Here, try this on.
－哈！
－不，别这样
￡- Ugh!
￡- No, come on.
配你刚买的那条围巾很好看
lt'll look great
with that scarf you bought.
要不要再买几双新运动鞋？
And maybe those new
platform sneakers.
我不再有意思了
l'm not fun anymore.
你在说什么啊？
What are you
talking about?
你很有意思，我们在一起很开心
You're fun.
We're having fun.
我们午餐还喝了红酒呢
We have wine at lunch.
好吧
Okay.
试试别的颜色？
Another color maybe?
怎么了？怎么回事？
What? What is it?
我是个无趣的家庭主妇
l'm a boring housewife!
－什么？
－我是个又老又胖的无趣的家庭主妇
￡- What?
￡- l'm a big old boring housewife!
所以雷才不想去佛蒙特
And that's why Ray isn't excited
about going to vermont.
我应该取消整个旅行
l should just cancel
the whole trip.
别这样，你一点也不无趣
Come on,
you're not boring.
你们会过得很开心的
You're going to have
an amazing, amazing time!
和你的老公在一起哦
With your husband!
看！
Look.
当娜・卡冉
Donna Karan.
我到底在想什么？
What was l thinking?
雷愿意去佛蒙特，完全是为了冰激凌
Ray's only going to vermont
for the ice cream.
那个节目只需要2个小时
余下的时间就剩我了
That tour lasts two hours
then it's just me.
价格贵得太离谱了！
These prices
are outrageous.
这都是怎么回事？
What's all this?
当你们出门的时候，我来照顾孩子
不记得了？
l'm babysitting for you while you're
on your getaway, remember?
噢，但是我们不到明天不会走的
Oh, okay, but we
don't leave until tomorrow,
所以我们明天才走
so leave until tomorrow.
嘿
Hey.
－这是我向你借的包
－好的
￡- Here's the bag that l borrowed.
￡- Yeah.
这是什么味道？
你用来装什么了？
What's this smell?
What did you keep in it?
一些肉
Some meat.
我看到妈妈在搬东西
So l see Ma's
laying in supplies.
欢迎你明天来这里吃晚饭
You're welcome to come over
here for dinner tomorrow night.
噢，我懂了
你们欢迎我偶尔过来串串门
Oh, l see.
So l'm a nice guy to have over,
但是不想我住在这里
but you wouldn't want me
staying here.
－怎么了？罗伯特
－没什么
￡- What, Robert?
￡- Nothing.
我不问，也不想
Wasn't asked,
wasn't considered.
你在想什么？亲爱的
What were you
considered for, dear?
看看，今天的节目是……
Let's see,
today's category...
照顾孩子
child care.
－听着，罗伯特，我不是想……
－噢，你不是想！
￡- Look, Robert. l didn't think￡-￡-
￡- Oh, you didn't think!
难道你不觉得一个在CPR受训，
Why would you think someone
who's trained in CPR,
受过公共安全和急救专业训练的人，
public safety
and conflict resolution
是完全有能力当个保姆的吗？
would be able
to babysit?
罗伯特，你想来照顾孩子？很好
Robert, you want to take
care of the kids? Fine.
－不需要妈妈来做这些
－她必须得做这些
￡- Mom doesn't have to do it.
￡- Yes she does have to do it.
那样我才能远离她
That's my getaway from her.
我可以过来这里帮忙
l can come
over here and help.
但那和你住在这里，而我呆在那里
That's not the same thing
as you staying here
完全不是一回事
and me staying there.
妈，我不需要你帮忙，OK？
Ma, l don't need
your help, okay?
－我可以照顾孩子
－好的，亲爱的，没问题
￡- l can take care of the kids.
￡- Okay, dear, okay.
什么？
What?
噢，好的
Oh, okay.
好的
Good!
怎么了？
What?
再见！
Goodbye!
那我也走了
l'll be going
along, too.
三天后再见
l'll see you
in three days.
－好的
－怎么回事？
￡- Yeah. Okay.
￡- What?
没什么，亲爱的
Nothing, dear.
拜拜
Bye￡-bye.
嘿，听着
我不想让你不高兴
Hey, look.
l won't let you down.
好好放松，享受旅行吧
Just relax and go enjoy
your trip.
是啊，我知道
Yeah, yeah.
l know.
你以前去过这些家庭旅馆吗？
You ever been to one
of these bed and breakfasts?
是的，和我的前妻
Yeah, with my ex￡-wife.
感觉怎么样？
How was it?
你没听到那句话的末尾吗？
Did you not catch
the end of that sentence?
好吧，很好
Yeah, great.
你那是什么表情啊？
What's with the face?
我不知道，只是……
l don't know.
Yeah, it's just...
要出去这么长的时间
going away together
is so much time
呆在一起
together.
你怕什么？
What are you afraid of?
－你们还……
－什么？
￡- You guys still￡-￡-
￡- What?
是啊是啊，我们有做
不过不是这个问题
Yeah, yeah, we do.
But that's not the problem.
是内在关系
lt's the in￡-between.
啊，你是说剩余的时间
Ah, the remains of the day.
她一直在说会有多么浪漫
She keeps saying how romantic
it's going to be.
整整三天的浪漫
Three days of romantic.
我都看不见市场需求
l don't see the need.
听着，我给你一点建议
Listen, let me give you
some advice.
这些旅行是为妻子准备的
These trips
are for the wife.
就像是度周末
lt's a weekend.
雷蒙德，雷蒙德
Raymond, Raymond,
Raymond, Raymond.
知道吗？有的时候，在监狱里
You know, sometimes
at the precinct
我们把一些罪犯关进一个房间过周末
we've got the throw guys
into the lock￡-up for a weekend.
你猜哪些人会最难熬？
And you know which guys
have the worst time there?
个子小的？
The small ones?
不是
No.
一直看表的人
The guys who are watching
the clock.
但是那些扳手腕，
But the guys
who arm￡-wrestle,
玩牌，吹口哨的人
play cards, whistle,
却觉得时间过得很快
those are the ones
for who time passes quickly.
是啊，但是我得说话
Yeah, but l have to talk.
而那些家伙却有权保持沉默
Those guys have the right
to remain silent.
－嗨
－嗨，宝贝
￡- Hi.
￡- Hey, honey.
－噢，你为旅行做了大采购啊
－是啊
￡- Oh, you got some stuff for the trip.
￡- Yeah.
－肯定会很有趣的
－是的
￡- lt's going to be fun.
￡- Yeah.
－我都等不及了
－是啊，只有我和你
￡- l can't wait.
￡- Yeah, just me and you.
－是啊
－你买了什么？
￡- Yeah.
￡- What did you get?
我买了一套不错的衣服
准备穿着它坐干草马车
Well, l got a great outfit
for the hayrides.
－干草马车？
－是啊
￡- Hayrides?
￡- Yeah.
好吧
Yeah.
听着，那种被关起来的周末，
So listen,
that weekend lock￡-up,
需要提前几天预约？
how far in advance
is that booked?
雷，让我来拎一个吧
You know, Ray,
l can carry one of those.
不用了
No, l'm fine.
哇噢
Wow.
看起来真不错
This looks nice.
是啊，很不错。我喜欢
Yeah, it's nice.
l like it.
我喜欢那个门吸
l like￡-￡-
l like the doorstop
还是兔子形状的！
in the shape of a bunny.
是啊
Yeah.
有人吗？
Hello?
“请按海龟”
"Please ring turtle."
－噢，你们好啊
－嗨
￡- Oh, hi there.
￡- Hi.
－你们一定是巴龙夫妇
－是的
￡- You must be the Barones.
￡- Yeah.
－我是黛博拉，这是雷
－嘿
￡- l'm Debra. And this is Ray.
￡- Hey.
我是塞丝莉・戴里
很抱歉让你们久等
Cecily Daly.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
我刚才在包一些野餐用的叉子
l was packing some folks
a picnic lunch.
噢，真浪漫
Oh, that's so romantic.
你喜欢？我们买一个
You like that?
We'll take one of those.
野餐已经订好了，晚上6点钟
Picnic orders have to be in
by 6:00 the night before.
这张单子上都有
lt's all right here
in the handout.
噢，好多兔子
Oh, more bunnies.
我想想把登记簿放哪儿了……
Now if l could just remember where
l put the reservation book.
房间里没有电视？
No Tv in the room?
这个周末你真的需要一台电视机吗？
Did you really want a Tv
this weekend?
不了，我们可以扳手腕
No, we'll arm￡-wrestle.
这是你们的钥匙
Here's your key.
公共浴室就在走廊对面
And the common bathroom
is just across the hall.
房间里连浴室也没有？
No bathrooms in
the rooms either?
我能问个问题吗？
Can l ask you
something?
房间里有什么？
What is in the room?
－我们现在是不是已经在房间里了？
－雷
￡- Are we in the room right now?
￡- Ray.
－好极了！
－比尔，潘姆！
￡- That's great!
￡- Bill, Pam.
我们早餐时没看见你们
We missed you two
at breakfast.
我们吃了蓝莓馅饼
We had blueberry
pancakes.
对不起，我们起不来
Sorry, we couldn't seem
to get out of bed.
－准备走了吗？宝贝
－当然，宝贝
￡- Ready to go, babe?
￡- Sure, babe.
你们要去哪儿？
Where you off to?
我们要去克拉佛兹勃利的古代展会结帐
We're gonna check out that antique
fair in Craftsbury Common.
我在介绍上看到过，那一定很不错
l read about that.
That's supposed to be great.
再见
See you.
你想去那个狡猾的蔓越桔园？
（和克拉佛兹勃利近音）
Did you want to go
to that cranberry crafty land?
今天我已经安排了本和杰瑞的旅行了
Well, l scheduled the Ben & Jerry's
thing for today.
因为你看起来很喜欢这个
'Cause you seemed
so excited about it.
是啊，但如果你不想去
我们不一定非得去的
Yeah, but we don't have to do that
if you don't want to.
不，我想去
这是我们的周末
No, l do.
This our weekend.
我们应该做一些大家都喜欢的事情
We're gonna do things
that we both enjoy.
不能感觉我们没有共同点
lt's not like
we have nothing in common.
是啊，是啊
公共浴室
Yeah.
Yeah, common bathroom.
好了，谁拿走了黄色的小块？
All right, who took
my yellow piece?
这不好玩！是我赢了
lt's not funny.
l was winning.
你们知道，拿走我的黄色小块的家伙
Do you know what happened
to the last person
会得到什么下场吗？
who took my yellow piece?
－ 怎么？
－ 他们要被挠痒痒！
￡- What?
￡- They got a big tickle, that's what.
我找不到开罐器了
l can't find
a can opener.
－什么？
－我没和你说话
￡- What?
￡- l'm not talking to you.
－你妈妈在哪儿？
－我不知道，她不在这儿
￡- Where's your mother?
￡- l don't know. She's not here.
你想来玩“糖果岛”吗？爷爷
You want to play
Candy Land, Grandpa?
我想要我的鲜烩蛤蜊！（和糖果岛近音）
l want my clam chowder.
－我肯定雷已经……
－玛丽
￡- l'm sure Ray has￡-￡-
￡- Marie!
－爸爸，她不在这儿
－玛丽
￡- Dad, she's not here.
￡- Marie!
－爸爸！
－你能不能别嚷嚷？
￡- Dad!
￡- Would you stop yelling?
开罐器在冰箱最上面的抽屉里
The can opener is in the top drawer
by the refrigerator.
谢谢
Thank you.
星期一见
See you Monday.
－你好吗，亲爱的
－你在这儿干什么？
￡- Hello, dear.
￡- What are you doing here?
打扫啊
Cleaning.
妈，听着
雷不在的时候我负责这里
Ma, listen, l'm in charge
while Raymond is away, all right?
当然是你负责，亲爱的
Of course you are,
dear.
你干得很不错
You're doing
a wonderful job.
－双胞胎该睡午觉了
－这些我会管的
￡- The twins could use a nap.
￡- l'm handling this.
我知道，亲爱的
我可以透过通风口听见
l know, dear.
l can hear through the vent.
－你准备晚餐吃什么？
－我叫了匹萨
￡- Have you thought about dinner?
￡- l'm ordering pizza.
不，匹萨不能当晚餐
我来做点东西吧
No, pizza's not dinner.
l'll fix something.
你知道她在这里吗？
Did you know
she was here?
奶奶总是在这儿
Grandma's always here.
－钥匙在你那里吗？
－不，在你那
￡- You got the key?
￡- No, you have it.
你真有趣
You're the funny one.
噢不，又是那对情侣
Oh no,
it's that couple.
快啊，钥匙去哪儿了？
该死的钥匙在哪？
Come on, where's the key?
Where's the damn key?
－嘿
－嗨，过得怎么样？
￡- Hey.
￡- Hi. How was your day?
简直难以置信
Unbelievable.
是啊，太棒了
我们步行走过野花园
Yeah, it was great.
We hiked through wildflowers
我们还摘了苹果
参观了本和杰瑞的冰激凌厂
then we picked apples.
And then we toured Ben & Jerry's
还有泰迪熊工厂
and the Teddy Bear Factory.
你们安排了不少节目啊
You guys did
a lot of stuff.
我们只去了克拉佛兹勃利
We just went
to Craftsbury Common.
比尔给我买了床被子
Bill bought me this quilt.
这是周年纪念日礼物
lt's an anniversary gift.
第一次约会的6个月纪念
Six months since
our first date.
－谢谢你，宝贝
－不客气，宝贝
￡- Thank you, babe.
￡- You're welcome, babe.
－他为每件事庆祝
－是啊
￡- He celebrates everything.
￡- Yeah.
在这里！
There it is.
我以为我把钥匙丢了
谁知竟在我的后面口袋了
l thought l lost the key but there
it was right in my back pocket.
多有趣啊
That's so funny.
哇噢
Wow.
我们曾经也那样吗？
Were we ever like that?
谁？宝贝和宝贝？
Who, babe and babe?
－是啊，他们看起来是那么……
－烦人？
￡- Yeah, they just seem so￡-￡-
￡- Annoying?
我想说快乐
l was thinking happy.
是啊，他们还没结婚哪
Well they're not
married yet.
所以，要是他们结婚了
该有多么开心啊
So, just think how happy
they're gonna get.
好吧，你要去淋浴吗？
Okay, so are you gonna
shower?
－为什么？
－等会要乘干草马车啊
￡- What for?
￡- For the hayride.
我闻起来有多臭？
How bad do l smell
需要我坐在一匹马拉的车子里，
that l got to take
a shower
还要事先洗个澡？
before being dragged around
behind a horse?
我想你是对的，我们不需要淋浴
l guess you're right.
We don't need to shower.
－有时间打个盹吗？
－没时间
￡- ls it time for a nap?
￡- l don't think so.
我们6点半就要下楼了
We've gotta be downstairs
by 6:30.
－晚饭怎么办？
－好像是包括在节目里的
￡- What about dinner?
￡- lt's kind of included.
应该是篝火野餐会什么的
lt's sort of a cookout,
campfire thing.
－有什么可吃的？
－我怎么知道有什么可吃的？
￡- What are they having?
￡- l don't know what they're having.
我只是觉得那应该会很有趣
l just thought
it would be fun.
你知道什么最有趣吗？
打个盹
You know what might
be more fun? A nap.
好吧，很好，你打盹吧
尽情打盹吧
Okay, fine, you nap.
Nap all you want.
知道吗？下一次，你来挑这见鬼的旅馆
You know what? The next time
you pick the frickin' hotel
你来安排节目
and you plan
all the activities
然后我来抱怨一切
and l'll be the one
that hates everything!
等等，黛博拉
别这样
Wait, Debra!
Come on.
我没说我讨厌这一切
l didn't say
l hated everything.
－你没必要说
－噢，怎么了
￡- You didn't have to say it.
￡- Oh, what￡-￡-
我做什么了？我怎么了？
what did l do?
What did l do?
我只不过说“有什么可吃的”
我怎么了？
l said what are they having?
What did l do?
拜托！你刚才说有个野餐会
Come on! You said there was going
to be a cookout thing,
于是我就问
“有什么可吃的？”
and l said,
"What are they having?"
这个问题很符合逻辑啊！
That's a perfectly
legitimate question.
没什么别的意思
There was no other
meaning there.
还有打盹的事情，那只是……
And the nap thing,
that was just￡-￡-
我希望浪漫一点！
仅此而已
that's me trying to be romantic.
That's all.
对不起，我不知道我在干什么
l'm sorry. l don't know what the hell
l'm doing here.
－里面有人吗？
－是的
￡- ls someone in there?
￡- Yeah.
你在想什么？
What do you think?
宝贝，出来吧
别人要用浴室了
Honey, come on. Somebody else
needs to use the bathroom.
宝贝，快啊
Honey, come on.
我们不能霸占着浴室
We're not the only one
who has this bathroom.
别忘了，这间只有公共浴室的旅馆
Remember, you're the one
who booked the place
可是你订的
with the share￡-
the￡-bathroom thing.
我把事情越搞越糟了，是不是？
l just made it worse,
didn't l?
宝贝，出来吧
Honey, come on.
对不起
l'm sorry.
求你了，出来吧
我们是朋友，嗯？
Please, come on.
Let's be friends, huh?
我们是出来度假啊
This is our
weekend getaway.
来啊，宝贝
开门……
Come on, honey.
Unlock the￡-￡-
噢
Oh.
门没锁
lt's not locked.
我们只要一会
We'll just be a minute.
嘿
Hey.
你看，这门上没锁
You know, there's no lock
on that thing.
你应该挂那个牌子
You're supposed
to hang the sign.
“耐心是一种美德”
"Patience is a virtue."
怎么了？雷
What, Ray?
没什么，这蛮有意思的
No, nothing.
lt's charming.
很实在
And true.
你想回家吗？
So you wanna
just go home?
除非你想
Only if you
really want to.
别这样，还没到这种地步吧？
Come on,
it's not really going that well.
除非你这么觉得
Unless you think
that it is.
我想让你觉得开心
l was trying to make
this fun for you.
我是说，你以为那些徒步游，
l mean, why￡-￡-
that hike
那些苹果园，还有冰激凌工厂
是为了什么？
and the apple orchard
and the ice cream factory￡-￡-
你以为我安排这些傻节目是为了什么？
why do you think l planned
all those stupid things?
等一等，你觉得这些事很傻？
Wait a minute.
You thought they were stupid?
当然了
Of course.
我以为只要让你一直马不停蹄地转
你就不会注意到
l just thought that if l kept you busy
you wouldn't notice￡-￡-
什么？
What?
注意到什么？
Notice what?
注意到你的老婆是多么无趣
That l'm your
boring wife.
什么？无趣的老婆？
What?
Boring wife?
你觉得你让我感到无趣了？
You thought
you'd be boring to me?
有什么好笑的？
What's so funny?
没什么？
Nothing.
你很在意我的感觉
You were nervous
about being boring to me.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
这很……很好玩
lt's just￡-￡-
it is funny.
你觉得你无趣，那我呢？
You thinking you're boring.
What about me?
在华盛顿桥上，
Come on, l ran out
of things to say
我没话可说的时候，
on the George
Washington Bridge.
还记得吗？
我居然说我习惯走在上层
Remember, l said l always
take the upper level
因为万一桥塌了，我就会跌在下面的人身上
because if it collapses you fall
on the people on the lower level?
这根本是莫明其妙
That doesn't
even make sense.
我们都会掉在河里，然后死掉
We're all gonna die.
We all go in the river.
这太傻了
lt's stupid.
是的
Yeah.
还有车子开到100英里时
你居然说，
And there was 100 miles
where all you said was,
“噢看啊，里程表要撞上80000了！”
"Oh look, the odometer
is going to hit 80,000."
我就是这个意思！
My point exactly.
这么说我们确实还是有共同点的
So we do have something
in common.
我们都很无趣
We're boring.
嗨，我们是无趣夫妇
Hi, we're the Borings.
我们刚突破了80000
We just hit 80,000.
你想干什么？
想去乘干草马车吗？
What do you want to do?
You want to do the hayride?
知道吗？
You know what?
打个小盹听起来很诱人
That nap sounded
pretty good.
－真的？
－没错
￡- Yeah?
￡- Yeah.
自从艾丽出生以后
l've been wanting
to take a nap
我就盼着能打个小盹了
since Ally was born.
嘿
Hey.
打个小盹对我来说可不无趣
Nothing boring to me
about a nap.
或许……
You know, and then...
等会还可以……
maybe a little later
－谁知道呢，嗯？
－好吧，肯定了。但先要打个小盹
￡- who knows, huh?
￡- Okay, definitely. But first a nap.
噢，肯定只打个小盹
Oh, definitely a nap.
打扰一下，我是塞丝莉
你们没事吧？
Excuse me, it's Cecily.
Everything all right?
是的，我们马上出来了
Yeah, yeah.
We're done.
好吧
Yeah.
噢
Oh.
－你干嘛要那么做？
－我不知道，一下子慌了
￡- Why did you do that?
￡- l don't know, l panicked.
来吧，现在我们该洗手了
Come on, now we got
to wash our hands.
嘿，兔子香皂
Hey, bunny soap.
我们为每件事庆祝
We celebrate everything.
几点了？
What time is it?
9:00.
－我们错过晚饭了
－嗯，我想是的
￡- We missed dinner.
￡- Mm, l guess.
你想继续睡？
You wanna just sleep
through?
是的
Yes.
这个假期真不错
This is a great vacation.
翻译：lisa doll
yukii45@hotmail.com
谢谢观赏